Guide to the Records of the Office of Media Production RG.7.3.4
New York University Archives
- Series I: Projects
  - Admissions Video (Reel 120-121, 123-131, 133, 135-143, 145), 1999 (Box 139, Folder Project 82)
  - School of Law CD-ROM (Reel 2, 7-10, 12-14), 1998 (Box 140, Folder Project 80)
  - Bobby Wagner Tribute Video (Reel 1-2), 1999 (Box 140, Folder Project 94)
  - TSOA- Keiko Ibi Oscar Party (Reel 1-2), 1999 (Box 140, Folder Project 96)
  - Alec Baldwin Dedicates Theater in Cantor Film Center (Reel 1-2), 1999 (Box 140, Folder Project 97)
  - Casa Italiana Donation Press Conference (Reel 1), 1988 (Box 140, Folder Project 100)
  - Frank McCourt Alumni Award Lecture (Reel 1-6), 1998 (Box 140, Folder Project 103)
  - King Juan Carlos Center Dedication (Project 160), 1997; cuid17541 (Box 140, Betacam cuid17541A, cuid17541B, cuid17541C, cuid17541D, Vhs cuid17541E)
  - Stern UG Parents' Weekend 2000 (Reel 1-8) (Box 140, Folder Project 258)
  - Alumni Video 2000 (Reels 20-22, 24, 26, 31-39, 44-49, 50-52) (Box 141, Folder Project 256)
  - Stern MBA Recruitment Video (Reel 1-14, 21-44, 52-53), 1996 (Box 142, Folder Project 114)
  - Silver Convocation (Reel 1-8), 2002 (Box 143, Folder Project 343)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards 2002 (Reel 1-12, 14-29) (Box 143, Folder Project 346)
  - Ireland House Documentary Reel 1-6, 8-11, 14-16), 2004 (Box 144, Folder Project 410)
  - Dean Sally Blount-Lyon Media Training Session (Reel 1), 2004 (Box 144, Folder Project 488)
  - Naomi Levine Class on Legal Issues and Ethics in Philanthropy and Fundraising (Reel 1-18), 2004 (Box 145, Folder Project 401)
  - NYU in Albany Day Video (Reel 13), 1996 (Box 146, Folder Project 30)
  - NYU in Albany Day Video Master (Reel 1), 1996 (Box 146, Folder Project 30)
  - Stern Lecture with Harvey Golub, American Express Master (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 146, Folder Project 39)
  - Stern Lecture with Jack Welsh: General Electric Master (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 146, Folder Project 42)
  - Going to College Master (Reel 1), 1992 (Box 146, Folder Project 47)
  - Commencement 1996 Master (Reel 1-2) (Box 146, Folder Project 50)
  - Beat Conference (Project 0065)
    - Town Hall Performance, 1994 May 19; 2 Betacam_SP (Box 146, Reel 17-18, Box Shared University Archives 106, Disc 16-17)
      Access copies available.
    - Loeb Concert, 1994; 2 Betacam_SP; Production element: Master (Box 146, Reel 19-20, Box Shared University Archives 106, Disc 18-19)
  - Claire Fagin Lecture for SoE Master (Reel 1), 1998 (Box 146, Folder Project 76)
  - Laurence A. Tisch Gala Master (Reel 1), 1999 (Box 146, Folder Project 83)
  - NYU: Life in Greenwich Village Master (Reel 1-3), undated (Box 147, Folder Project 1)
  - Vaclav Havel at NYU Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 147, Folder Project 2)
  - NYU in Prague Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 223, Folder Project 3)
  - Commencement 1991 Master (Project #0006), cuid18409 (Box 147, U-matic cuid18409A, cuid18409B)
    Scope and Contents
    Produced and directed by Elisa Guarino.
    Duration: 69 minutes in 2 parts
  - Commencement 1993 Master (Reel 1-2) (Box 223, Folder Project 9)
    Includes master and dub U-matic tapes.
  - Prime Minister Kaifu at NYU Master (Reel 1-2), undated (Box 147, Folder Project 13)
  - Weehawken Press Conference Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 223, Folder Project 14)
  - Watch Team Video Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 223, Folder Project 15)
  - Prime Minister Haughey at NYU Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 223, Folder Project 20)
  - Poetry Reading, Faculty Resource Network Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 147, Folder Project 21)
  - Myra Alperson at FAS Journalism Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 223, Folder Project 27)
  - Lee Brown at NYU Master (Reel 1), 1991 (Box 148, Folder Project 11)
  - Faculty Resource Network Master (Reel 1), 1996 (Box 148, Folder Project 22)
  - Irish Muse Master (Reel 1), undated (Box 148, Folder Project 44)
  - Irish Prime Minister Albert Reynolds - Address to NYU Community Master (Reel 1), 1992 (Box 148, Folder Project 46)
  - Going to College Master (Reel 1), 1992 (Box 148, Folder Project 47)
  - The Tradition Continues: New York University's 14th President Master (Reel 1), 1991 (Box 148, Folder Project 53)
  - Wagner Graduate School of Public Service Master (Reel 1-3), undated (Box 148, Folder Project 54)
  - Benefactor's Luncheon Master (Reel 1), 1990 (Box 148, Folder Project 57)
  - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame 1993 Elisa Guarino Master (Reel 1) (Box 148, Folder Project 60)
  - NYU in the News Master (Reel 1), 1991 (Box 148, Folder Project 62)
  - NYU in the Movies Master (Reel 1), 1991 (Box 148, Folder Project 64)
  - School of Social Work Dedication Master(Reel 1), 1994 (Box 148, Folder Project 69)
  - Onassis Center Video Master (Reel 1-2), 1990 (Box 149, Folder Project 12)
  - New York University Commencement Master (Reel 1), 1989 (Box 149, Folder Project 25)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend Video Master (Reel1), undated (Box 149, Folder Project 26)
  - Alumni Hall Video Master (Reel 1), 1992 (Box 149, Folder Project 28)
  - Commencement 1992 Master (Reel 1-2) (Box 149, Folder Project 34)
  - Commencement 1992 Highlights Master (Reel 1) (Box 149, Folder Project 35)
  - Commencement 1992 Video Promo Master (Reel 1) (Box 149, Folder Project 36)
  - NYU Music Sing-A-Long Master (Reel 1-2), 1994 (Box 149, Folder Project 37)
  - Stern Lecture with Sidner Harmon Master (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 149, Folder Project 40)
  - Stern Lecture with Christie Hefner, CEO, Playboy Master (Reel 1), 1995 (Box 149, Folder Project 41)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part I: Russia and the Power of Geography, undated (Box 150, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part II: Russia and the Power of Ideology, undated (Box 150, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part III: Russia and the West, undated (Box 150, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part I: Russia and the Power of Geography, undated (Box 151, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part II: Russia and the Power of Ideology, undated (Box 151, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part III: Russia and the West, undated (Box 151, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part I: Russia and the Power of Geography, undated (Box 152, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part II: Russia and the Power of Ideology, undated (Box 152, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part III: Russia and the West, undated (Box 152, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part I: Russia and the Power of Geography, undated (Box 153, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part II: Russia and the Power of Ideology, undated (Box 153, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part III: Russia and the West, undated (Box 153, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part I: Russia and the Power of Geography, undated (Box 154, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part II: Russia and the Power of Ideology, undated (Box 154, Folder Project 33)
  - The Russian Tea Room Lecture Series, Part III: Russia and the West, undated (Box 154, Folder Project 33)
  - The Miracle on Washington Square: The New York University Story, undated (Box 154, Folder Project 225)
  - Wagner/Brussels Televideo Class: Feed from Brussels (Reel 1), undated (Box 154, Folder Project 170)
  - Wagner/Brussels Televideo Class: Conference Tape 1 (Reel 13), undated (Box 154, Folder Project 170)
  - Wagner/Brussels Televideo Class: Conference Tape 2 (Reel 14), undated (Box 154, Folder Project 170)
  - Wagner/Brussels Televideo Class: Dub of Master (Reel 12), undated (Box 154, Folder Project 170)
  - Employment Video (Reels 1-19), undated (Box 155, Folder Project 471)
  - West Along the Road (Reels 1-42), undated (Box 156, Folder Project 393)
  - West Along the Road (Reels 43-82), undated (Box 157, Folder Project 393)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement 2005 video (Reels 40-49) (Box 157, Folder Project 427)
  - West Along the Road (Reels 83-98), undated (Box 158, Folder Project 393)
  - Lisa Goldberg Memorial Video (Reels 1-72), undated (Box 159, Folder Project 517)
  - Stern MBA Precommencement Video 2006 (Reels 1-47) (Box 160, Folder Project 475)
  - Stern Undergraduate Precommencement Video 2003 (Reels 1-21) (Box 161, Folder Project 372)
  - Stern Baccalaureate Video 2006 (Reels 1-5, 7-20) (Box 161, Folder Project 484)
  - Stern MBA CEO Lecture 2003 (Reels 1-3) (Box 161, Folder Project 379)
  - Stern in the News (Reel 1), undated (Box 161, Folder Project 301)
  - Law Mini CD-ROM 2003 (Reels 1-4) (Box 161, Folder Project 387)
  - NYU School of Law CD 2006 (Reel 1) (Box 161, Folder Project 480)
  - Stern Precommencement Video 2005 (Reels 1-39) (Box 162, Folder Project 427)
  - Stern Precommencement Video 2007 (Reels 8, 13-51) (Box 163, Folder Project 499)
  - Stern Undergraduate Precommencement Video, 2005 (Box 164, Folder Project 440)
  - John Brademas 80th Birthday Celebration, undated (Box 164, Folder Project 524)
  - Trustee Pre-Commencement Dinner, 2007 (Box 164, Folder Project 532)
  - Stern Derivatives Conference, 2007 (Box 164, Folder Project 533)
  - President John Sexton's Presentation on Global Campaign, undated (Box 164, Folder Project 552)
  - Undergraduate Parents' Weekend, 2004 (Box 165, Folder Project 426)
  - Dorothy Height interview, undated (Box 165, Folder Project 444)
  - Stern Undergraduate Parents' Weekend Video, 2005 (Box 165, Folder Project 459)
  - Dr. Epstein Tribute Video, undated (Box 165, Folder Project 526)
  - Commencement 2004 (Reels 1-3) (Box 166, Folder Project 418)
  - CADA DVD (Reels 1-22), undated (Box 166, Folder Project 458)
  - Stern Undergraduate Baccalaureate Video (Reels 1-17), 2007 (Box 166, Folder Project 513)
  - Stern Undergraduate Pre-Commencement (Reels 1-8), 2004 (Box 167, Folder Project 408)
  - Stern Admissions Podcast (Reels 1-3), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 502)
  - Lisa Goldberg Memorial Service (Reels 1-2), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 518)
  - Lisa Goldberg Memorial Slideshow (Reels 1-2), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 519)
  - Stern Undergraduate Baccalaureate Graduation Ceremony (Reels 1-2), 2003 (Box 167, Folder Project 527)
  - Leadership Conference--Kimmel Center (Reel 1), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 528)
  - Community Fund 25th Anniversary (Reels 1-23, 25), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 549)
  - President John Sexton Presentation on Global Campaign (Reels 1-12), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 552)
  - Dr. Moursi--Pediatric Dentistry (Reel 1), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 554)
  - Dr. Amr Moursi--Halloween (Reels 1-2), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 555)
  - Women and Leadership at NYU (Reels 1-2), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 556)
  - Craig Newmark at the Heyman Center for Philanthropy and Fundraising (Reels 1-7), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 557)
  - Silver School of Social Work Convocation (Reels 1-9), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 558)
  - Timothy Higdon Course (Reels 1-11), Fall 2007 (Box 167, Folder Project 561)
  - Joel Fleishman Presentation for the Heyman Center for Philanthropy and Fundraising (Reels 1-7), undated (Box 167, Folder Project 562)
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (Reels 1-21), undated (Box 168, Folder Project 226)
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (Reels 59-94), undated (Box 169, Folder Project 226)
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (Reels 22-52, 54-57), undated (Box 170, Folder Project 226)
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (Reels 95-130, 132-135), undated (Box 171, Folder Project 226)
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (Reels 131, 136-175), undated (Box 172, Folder Project 226)
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (Reels 176-213, 222-230, 233-252), undated (Box 173, Folder Project 226)
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (Reels 254-262, 265, 269-270, 272-287 and 25 unlabeled tapes, 7 unlabeled zip disks, 3 unlabeled VHS tapes, and 1 unlabeled CD), undated (Box 174, Folder Project 226)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Recruitment Video (Reels 1-40), undated (Box 175, Folder Project 123)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Recruitment Video (Reels 41-64, 68-78, 83, 84), undated (Box 176, Folder Project 123)
  - Case Fellowship May 16,17 and 18 1994 School of Education (transcript) (Box 177, File binder)
  - Brennan Center (transcript), undated (Box 177, File binder)
  - Billion Dollar Gala Video (transcript and video editing/production information), 1995 (Box 177, File binder)
  - Billion Dollar Gala Photographs, 1995 (Box 177, File binder)
  - America Reads Training Video (transcript), undated (Box 177, File binder)
  - Alumni Video 2001 (transcript) (Box 177, File binder)
  - Admissions Video (transcript), 1998 (Box 177, File binder)
  - Admissions Video 1996 (transcript) (Box 177, File binder)
  - Law Video 1997-1998 Interview (transcript) (Box 178, File binder)
  - School of Law Video (transcript), 1996 (Box 178, File binder)
  - Law School New Building (transcript), 2001 (Box 178, File binder)
  - Law Phase II (transcript), 1996 (Box 178, File binder)
  - Law III May 1998 (transcripts) (Box 178, File binder)
  - Law Development Video (transcripts), 1999 (Box 178, File binder)
  - L.J.O. Video (transcript), undated (Box 178, File binder)
  - L.J. Oliva Pictures (photocopies), 2002 (Box 178, File binder)
  - Larry Tisch Video (transcript), 1999 (Box 178, File binder)
  - La Pietra Video (transcript), 1998 (Box 178, File binder)
  - Brademas Center Reflections Project (Reels 1-10, 12-58), 2006 (Box 179, Folder Project 496)
  - Brademas Center Reflections Project Photos (2 CDs), 2006 (Box 179, Folder Project 496)
  - Undergraduate Admissions Diversity Book Video (Project 0473), 2005
    - B-Roll of Jose Torres at the Soup Kitchen, B-Roll of Richard Kamerman entering 721, 2005 December 5; Meltzer, Doug; Guarino, Elisa; Foerder, Dave; 1 Betacam_SP; Video: 1/2" Betacam SP (Box 180, Reel 4)
    - B-Roll of Juliana Merola in her class, 2005 November 30; Cassara, Bill; Guarino, Elisa; Foerder, Dave; 1 Betacam_SP; Video: 1/2" Betacam SP (Box 180, Reel 12)
    - B-Roll of Students Getting Their Pictures Taken, 2005 December 15; 1 MiniDV (Box 180, Reel 16)
    - Diversity v5A, undated; 1 DVD-R (Box 180, Reel 28)
  - Welcome to New York University (Reels 2-10), undated (Box 180, Folder Project 107)
  - Stern MBA Centennial Celebration (transcript), 1999 (Box 181, File binder)
  - Stern Community Service (transcripts), 2001 (Box 181, File binder)
  - Reprographics (transcript), 2000 (Box 181, File binder)
  - Reading Recovery (transcript), 1994 (Box 181, File binder)
  - NYU Online (2 binders), 1999 (Box 181, File binder)
  - NYU Stern School of Business Recruitment Video 2002 (transcript) (Box 181, File binder)
  - NYU in London (transcript), 1996 (Box 181, File binder)
  - NYU in France (transcript), 1995 (Box 181, File binder)
  - NYU Downtown Hospital (transcript), 1998 (Box 181, File binder)
  - Frank McCourt (transcript), 2002 (Box 181, File binder)
  - Law School Video (transcripts), undated (Box 181, File binder)
  - Law School CD-ROM/Video (transcript), 2002 (Box 181, File binder)
  - Law School Video (transcript), 2000-2001 (Box 181, File binder)
  - World Trade Center Reaction (transcript), 2001 (Box 182, File binder)
  - Wagner Website (transcript), 2001-2002 (Box 182, File binder)
  - Robert F. Wagner Memorial Video (2 binders), undated (Box 182, File binder)
  - TSOA (transcript), 1996 (Box 182, File binder)
  - Students and Jobs Video (transcripts), undated (Box 182, File binder)
  - Stern Undergraduate Recruitment Video (transcript), 2000 (Box 182, File binder)
  - Stern Undergraduate Recruitment 2002 (2 binders) (Box 182, File binder)
  - Stern Video (transcript), 1994 (Box 182, File binder)
  - Stern Undergraduate CD-ROM (transcript), 2000 (Box 182, File binder)
  - Stern MBA Recruit 2003 (transcript) (Box 182, File binder)
  - Stern MBA Recruitment Video (transcript), 1999 (Box 182, File binder)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement (transcript), 2002 (Box 182, File binder)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement (Reels 1-45), 2004 (Box 183, Folder Project 390)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement (Reels 46-60), 2004 (Box 184, Folder Project 390)
  - Stern Undergraduate Parents' Weekend (Reels 1-9), 2003 (Box 184, Folder Project 391)
  - Kimmel Center Video (transcripts), 2000 (Box 185, File binder)
  - Ireland House (transcript), undated (Box 185, File binder)
  - John Sexton Installation Video (transcript), 2002 (Box 185, File binder)
  - International Student Film Festival (transcript), 1998 (Box 185, File binder)
  - Greylock (transcript), 1998 (Box 185, File binder)
  - Grey Art Gallery Makeup Video (transcript), 2000 (Box 185, File binder)
  - Global Law Summit in Florence, Italy (transcript), 2000 (Box 185, File binder)
  - Gallatin Recruitment Video (transcript), 1999 (Box 185, File binder)
  - Gallatin (transcript), undated (Box 185, File binder)
  - Gala 2002 (transcript) (Box 185, File binder)
  - Gallatin Video/CD-ROM (transcript), 2003 (Box 185, File binder)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards 2002 (transcript) (Box 185, File binder)
  - Distinguished Teaching Medal Videos 2000 (transcript) (Box 185, File binder)
  - Distinguished Teaching Medal Videos 1999 (transcript) (Box 185, File binder)
  - Dentistry Video (transcript), 1997 (Box 186, File binder)
  - Dorothy Height (transcript), 2005 (Box 186, File binder)
  - Project 444 tape 2 of 2 Dorothy Height, April 6, 2005; 1 items (Box 186, Cassette video)
  - Dental School Oral History Interview (transcripts), 1999 (Box 186, File binder)
  - Dental School Video (transcripts), 1997 (Box 186, File binder)
  - Debra Janes Memorial (transcripts), 2000 (Box 186, File binder)
  - Dean Daly Tribute Video (transcript), 2002 (Box 186, File binder)
  - NYU Commencement 1996 Live Show (transcript) (Box 186, File binder)
  - Commencement 1995 (transcript) (Box 186, File binder)
  - Commencement 1993 (transcripts--2 binders) (Box 186, File binder)
  - Distinguished Teacher Award 2001 (transcripts) (Box 186, File binder)
  - Brademas Center Reflections Project (Reels 59-61, 64-91), ca. 2006 (Box 187, Folder Project 496)
  - NYU Commencement 2008 - Yankee Stadium (Reels 1, 4, 5, 11-33) (Box 187, Folder Project 578)
  - FERPA Video (Reels 1-9), 2006 (Box 187, Folder Project 495)
  - NYU School of Law Video (Reels 2, 38), undated (Box 188, Folder Project 71)
  - School of Law CD-ROM (Reels 1, 3-6, 11), 2002 (Box 188, Folder Project 80)
  - Admissions Video (Reels 35, 36) (Box 188, Folder Project 82)
  - Camp Greylock Screening and Panel (Reels 1-3), 1999 (Box 188, Folder 179)
  - School of Law Video 2000 (Reel 1) (Box 188, Folder Project 232)
  - Law School New Building (Reel 46), 2001 (Box 188, Folder Project 283)
  - Law School CD-ROM/Video (Reels 3-5), 1998 (Box 188, Folder Project 354)
  - La Pietra Leadership Conference (Reels 1-9), undated (Box 188, Folder Project 419)
  - Bob Tisch Tribute Video (Reels 31-34), 2002 (Box 206, Folder Project 436)
  - Development Campaign Video (Project 0420), 2004
    - B-roll of the Washington Square Arch and Empire State Building, 2004 August 31; Garland, Jimmy; Mihai, Adrian; 1 Betacam_SP; Video: 1/2" BetacamSP (Box 189, Reel 26)
    - B-roll of Daniel Weinberg at President's Picnic/B-Roll Washington Square Buildings, 2004 September 1; Garland, Jimmy; Mihai, Adrian; 1 Betacam_SP; Video: 1/2" BetacamSP (Box 189, Reel 28)
    - Interview with Dr. Richard Shapiro, 2004; 2 Betacam_SP (Box 189, Reel 36-37)
    - B-roll of Cancer Center Lobby, 2004 (Box 189, Reel 37)
    - B-Roll of University Charter, Compression Shot of Bobst Interior, B-Roll of Students, 2004 September 11; Meltzer, Doug; Kallenbach, Larry; 1 Betacam_SP; Video: 1/2" BetacamSP (Box 189, Reel 46)
    - B-Roll of Chrysler Building, Grand Central Terminal, street compression, Empire, 2004 September 14; Kallenbach, Larry; Meltzer, Doug; 1 Betacam_SP; Video: 1/2" BetacamSP (Box 189, Reel 48)
    - Aerial B-Roll of Washington Square Park, 2004 September 15; Getty Images, Inc.; 1 Betacam_SP; Video: 1/2" BetacamSP (Box 189, Reel 51)
    - B-roll of Jason Snell and Interviews (with timecodes) of Dr. Lennie, Molain Saintilus, undated (Box 189, Reel 67)
    - Development Campaign Video--With Credits, 2004 September; USA Studios; Richman, Matt; Guarino, Elisa; 1 DVD-R TRT: 15:42 (Box 189, Reel unknown)
  - VidiPax Job #3708 (Reels 1-4), undated (Box 189, Folder Project 420)
  - TSOA Salute 2001 Graduation Roll (Box 190, Folder Project 317)
  - Bobst Library: Interviews with Mr. Herbert Silverman and Dr. James Hester, interviewed by Nancy Cricco (Reels 1-3), 2002 (Box 190, Folder Project 365)
  - Jim Taylor Receiving the Academy Award for Best Adapted Screenplay of 2004 (Reel 1) (Box 190, Folder Project 439)
  - Center for Philanthropy Website Video 2005; Narration with Naomi Levine and William Josephson (Reels 1-4) (Box 190, Folder Project 445)
  - NYU Trustees Pre-commencement Dinner 2005 Announcements (Reel 1), May 2005 (Box 190, Folder Project 448)
  - Grad Alley 2005 (Reels 1-2), May 2005 (Box 190, Folder Project 449)
  - Law School CD-ROM 2005 (Reels 1,3) (Box 190, Folder Project 450)
  - HR Orientation Video (Reels 1-7), 2004 (Box 190, Folder Project 454)
  - Media Production Website: Betacam Stills for Homepage (Reel 1), 2007 (Box 190, Folder Project 512)
  - Stern MBA Recruitment Video 2003 (Reels 1-7, 10-24) (Box 191, Folder Project 381)
  - Frank McCourt Documentary (Reels 3-14, 16-37), 1999-2003 (Box 191, Folder Project 269)
  - Masters in Global Public Health Video for Web (Reels 1-29, 31-37, 40-57), 2002-2008 (Box 192, Folder Project 441)
  - Campus Exteriors with Students and Flags (Reel 10), 1997 November 10 (Box 193, Folder Project 59)
  - School of Law Campaign, 1999 April (Box 193, Folder Project 88)
  - Billion Dollar Gala, 2001 (Box 193, Folder Project 118)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Recruitment, 1997 October (Box 193, Folder Project 123)
  - Future Filmmakers Workshop, Undated (Box 193, Folder Project 139)
  - Year 2000 Celebration (Box 193, Folder Project 184)
  - Alumni Video 2000 (Box 193, Folder Project 256)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement 2001, 2001 May (Box 193, Folder Project 259)
  - Kimmel Center Video (Masters 2-4), 2001 February (Box 193, Folder Project 278)
  - NYU on the Air, 2001 April (Box 193, Folder Project 282)
  - Law School New Building, 2001 March 29 (Box 193, Folder Project 283)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement 2002 (Box 193, Folder Project 336)
  - President Olivia Tribute Video, 2002 April (Box 193, Folder Project 340)
  - Dean Daly Tribute Video, 2002 May (Box 206, Folder Project 351)
  - Gallatin 30th Anniversary Video, 2003 May (Box 193, Folder Project 374)
  - Stern MBA Recruitment Video 2003, 2003 October (Box 193, Folder Project 381)
  - Stern Undergraduate Parents' Weekend 2003, 2003 October (Box 193, Folder Project 391)
  - Development Campaign Video, 2004 September (Box 206, Folder Project 420)
  - Stern Undergraduate Parents' Weekend 2004 (Box 193, Folder Project 426)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement 2005 (Master 1-2), 2005 May (Box 206, Folder Project 427)
  - Stern MBA Admissions Website Alumni Video, 2004 (Box 206, Folder Project 434)
  - Bob Tisch Video, 2005 January (Box 193, Folder Project 436)
  - Dean Michael Alfano's Address to Bioterrorists, Undated (Box 193, Folder Project 438)
  - Stern Undergraduate Pre-Commencement 2005, 2005 May (Box 193, Folder Project 440)
  - Height, Dorothy, 2005 May (Box 206, Folder Project 444)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Commencement 2008 (Reel 11-14), 2008 March (Box 193, Folder Project 548)
  - La Pietra Video Footage (2 Masters, Reel 33-34, 36-38, 41, 44, 171), 2001 February (Box 194, Folder Project 7)
  - College of Dentistry Oral History, 2001 April (Box 194, Folder Project 178)